Papers of Charles Fletcher Lummis 1860-1956(bulk 1890-1920)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Photographs, circa 1891-1921; Series VI:; 8 folders
  - New Mexico, circa 1889-1899; no date (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - New Mexico, copy negatives and proofs, 12 envelopes, no date (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Portraits, 1900-1921 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Pottery and Jewelry, no date (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, no date (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Supplemental Materials, 1896-1921; Series VII:; 5 folders
  Arrangement: Unarragned
  Contains mostly miscellaneous bills, labels and envelopes, and an inventory of rooms at El Alisal.
  - Financial records, 1896-1921 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Partial inventory of El Alisal Rooms, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous labels and envelopes, no date (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Fishing equipment, no date (Box 19, Folder 5)